Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Video Recordings, 545120
  - Video 1042: 1984 Video Festival films: "Perceptions: A Question of Justice" by Sandra Gin Yep (25 min); "Perceptions: Japanese American Redress" by Sandra Gin Yep (25 min), CCTV labeled "U146", cuid2306; 545404 (Box 158)
  - Video 1043: 1984 Video Festival film "Perceptions: Japanese American Redress" by Sandra Gin Yep (25 min), CCTV labeled "U146", cuid2307; 545403 (Box 158)
  - Video 1044: Philippine Cinema London Video (also called Film in the Philippines) by Ron Orders, Large Door Unlimited, 37 mins, CCTV labeled "U184", cuid2308; 545402 (Box 158)
  - Video 1045: Shradanjali, CCTV labeled "U142", cuid2309; 545401 (Box 158)
  - Video 1046: Tibet (Documentary), Producer/Director: Nien-Sheng Lin, Ph.D., 49 mins, CCTV labeled "U137", cuid2310; 545400 (Box 158)
  - Video 1047: Yuki Shimoda: Asian American Actor by Amy Kato and John Esako, 30 mins, CCTV labeled "U211", cuid2311; 545399 (Box 158)
  - Video 1048: 1984 Video Festival films: "As the Wheels Turn" by Fredric Mao (11 mins 30 sec); "Video Installations by Shigeko Kubato (12 mins); "Japan Love, Honto" by Ann Eugenia Volkes (12 mins); "Reaching for the Stars" by Nancy Tong (24 mins), CCTV lab, cuid2312; 545398 (Box 159)
  - Video 1049: Asian Women Video Artists: "Birds" by Rii Kanazaki (8 mins), "Brighton" by Rii Kanazaki (3 mins 30 sec), "Hawaii" by Rii Kanazaki (15 mins 30 sec), "Manong" by Linda Mabalot (30 mins), CCTV labeled "U151", cuid2313; 545397 (Box 159)
  - Video 1050: Dollar a day, 10 cents a dance produced by George Ow Jr. (28.40 min), CCTV labeled "U159", cuid2314; 545396 (Box 159)
  - Video 1051: 1984 AAIFF film: East to West by Yaping Wang, 60 mins, CCTV labeled "U156/U166", cuid2315; 545395 (Box 159)
  - Video 1052: 1984 AAIFF film: First Look by Kavery Dutta, 60 mins, CCTV labeled "U155", cuid2316; 545394 (Box 159)
  - Video 1053: Kind of Yellow by David Chan (20 min) and Community Plot by JT Takaji (20 min), CCTV labeled "U157/U167", cuid2317; 545393 (Box 159)
  - Video 1054: Pacific Bridges: To a New Land by Noel Izon, 30 mins, CCTV labeled "U169/U179", cuid2318; 545392 (Box 159)
  - Video 1055: Pearls #1: Emi by Michael Toshiyuki Uno, 28 mins, CCTV labeled "U165/U175", cuid2319; 545391 (Box 159)
  - Video 1056: Pearls #2: Mako by Frank Nesbitt, 29 mins, CCTV labeled "U166/U176", cuid2320; 545390 (Box 159)
  - Video 1057: Broken Diary: Ch. 11, cuid2321; 545389 (Box 160)
  - Video 1058: The Open Window (Music by Jason Hwang), cuid2322; 545388 (Box 160)
  - Video 1059: Senjyu Can Non Kyu Seigen 1986 AAIVF (5:17), cuid2323; 545387 (Box 160)
  - Video 1060: The Shining Hour (1986 AAIVF) Morifumi Arimura, cuid2324; 545386 (Box 160)
  - Video 1061: Tomiyo Sasaki, cuid2325; 545385 (Box 160)
  - Video 1062: They Speak of Hope by Fern Lee Hagedon, cuid2326; 545384 (Box 160)
  - Video 1063: Tsumiki + Building Blocks 2 by Hiromu Saiki, cuid2327; 545383 (Box 160)
  - Video 1064: Two Comedians: Phil Nee + Stan Egi at the Middle of the Road, cuid2328; 545382 (Box 160)
  - Video 1065: Winter Chill Malcolm S. Wong, cuid2329; 545381 (Box 160)
  - Video 1066: Year of the Rat by Sasha Lee, cuid2330; 545380 (Box 160)
  - Video 1067: Arnie Wong Tigerly Inc., cuid2331; 545379 (Box 161)
  - Video 1068: Cheung on Chi, cuid2332; 545378 (Box 161)
  - Video 1069: Fear of Failure Malcolm S. Wong Tape 1, cuid2333; 545377 (Box 161)
  - Video 1070: Grass or When the Rain Falls - Janice Tanaka 1986 AAIVF (5:30), New York Hot Springs Taka Iimura 1986 AAIVF (11:00), cuid2334; 545376 (Box 161)
  - Video 1071: Hard Contact Hiroya Sakurai 1986 AAIVF, cuid2335; 545375 (Box 161)
  - Video 1072: India Cabaret by Mira Nair 11/15/85, cuid2336; 545374 (Box 161)
  - Video 1073: Naked Spaces Tape 1, cuid2337; 545373 (Box 161)
  - Video 1074: Naked Spaces Tape 2, cuid2338; 545372 (Box 161)
  - Video 1075: Naked Spaces Tape 3, cuid2339; 545371 (Box 161)
  - Video 1076: 1987 AAIFF Trailer Dub and Titles, cuid2340; 545370 (Box 162)
  - Video 1077: Do Si Te by Alan Nakagawa, cuid2341; 545369 (Box 162)
  - 10:11 min, cuid2342; 545368 (Box 162)
  - Video 1078: Flight of Ideas by Fu-Ding Chen, cuid2343; 545367 (Box 162)
  - Video 1079: The Long Weekend by Gregg Araki, cuid2344; 545366 (Box 162)
  - Video 1080: The Long Weekend by Gregg Araki, cuid2345; 545365 (Box 162)
  - Video 1081: Orientations by Richard Fung, 4th AAIVF, cuid2346; 545364 (Box 162)
  - Video 1082: Paris by Ping Chong / Meredith Mok, 4th AAIVF, cuid2347; 545363 (Box 162)
  - Video 1083: Spalding Gray's Map of L.A. by Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, 4th AAIVF, cuid2348; 545362 (Box 162)
  - Video 1084: 10th annual Nihonmachi Street Fair by S. Nakasako, cuid2349; 545361 (Box 162)
  - Video 1085: Asian Studs Nightmare, cuid2350; 545360 (Box 163)
  - Video 1086: "Camp Arirang" by Diana S. Lee and Grace Yoon-Kyung Lee, cuid2351; 545359 (Box 163)
  - Video 1087: Dirty Laundry by Richard Fung, cuid2352; 545358 (Box 163)
  - Video 1088: Fingers and Kisses, Coming Home by Shu Lea Cheang, cuid2353; 545357 (Box 163)
  - Video 1089:Fingers and Kisses, Coming Home by Shu Lea Cheang, cuid2354; 545356 (Box 163)
  - Video 1090: Footsteps, cuid2355; 545355 (Box 163)
  - Video 1091: L.A. Christmas by Kip Fulbeck, cuid2356; 545354 (Box 163)
  - Video 1092: Leaving Bakul Bagan, cuid2357; 545353 (Box 163)
  - Video 1093: A Letter from Home (a work in progress), cuid2358; 545352 (Box 163)
  - Video 1094: Merits of Life, cuid2359; 545351 (Box 164)
  - Video 1095: "Then", cuid2360; 545350 (Box 164)
  - Video 1096: Videos by Kimberly Saree Tomes, cuid2361; 545349 (Box 164)
  - Video 1097: "Singapore Report: Industrial Revolution", cuid2362; 545348 (Box 164)
  - Video 1098: Stopover by Larry Hoki, cuid2363; 545347 (Box 164)
  - Video 1099: Sweet Jail: The Sikhs of Yuba City by Beheroze F. Shroff, cuid2364; 545346 (Box 164)
  - Video 1100: Tongpan by Surachay Jantimathorn, cuid2365; 545345 (Box 164)
  - Video 1101: AKA Don Bonus, cuid2366; 545344 (Box 164)
  - Video 1102: Off Limits by Rea Tajiri, cuid2367; 545343 (Box 164)
  - Video 1103: "Out in the Open" by Renu Lobo, cuid2368; 545342 (Box 164)
  - Video 1104: Bittersweet Survival by Christine Choy / J.T. Takagi (27 min), cuid2369; 545341 (Box 165)
  - Video 1105: Coming to America by Renu Lobo, cuid2370; 545340 (Box 165)
  - Video 1106: Poppo at E'Village 4 (Oct 24), cuid2371; 545339 (Box 165)
  - Video 1107: Rebop:, cuid2372; 545338 (Box 165)
  - Video 1108: Sewing Woman by Arthur Dong, cuid2373; 545337 (Box 165)
  - Video 1109: Then by Takuhiro Tanaka and Shigeyeshi Ohi, cuid2374; 545336 (Box 165)
  - Video 1110: Third World Cultural Perspective Tape 1 by Nancy Tong/ Cecile Guidote, cuid2375; 545335 (Box 165)
  - Video 1111: The Young Concubine Part I by Wong King-Keung, 1981; cuid2376; 545334 (Box 165)
  - Video 1112: The Young Concubine Part II by Wong King-Keung, 1981; cuid2377; 545333 (Box 165)
  - Video 1113: Dangerous Encounter for the First Kind Part I by RTV, cuid2378; 545332 (Box 166)
  - Video 1114: Crack Shadow Boxers Part I, cuid2379; 545331 (Box 166)
  - Video 1115: Crack Shadow Boxers Part II, cuid2380; 545330 (Box 166)
  - Video 1116: Dangerous Encounter for the First King Part II by RTV, cuid2381; 545329 (Box 166)
  - Video 1117: The Imp (Pt. I), cuid2382; 545328 (Box 166)
  - Video 1118: The Mysterious Foot-Work of Kung Fu Part I, cuid2383; 545327 (Box 166)
  - Video 1119: The Mysterious Foot-Work of Kung Fu Part II, cuid2384; 545326 (Box 166)
  - Video 1120: Rainbow by Fung Fay Fay, cuid2385; 545325 (Box 166)
  - Video 1121: Reincarnated Part I by RTV, 1984; cuid2386; 545324 (Box 166)
  - Video 1122: The New Wife by Renee Cho (31 min), cuid2387; 545323 (Box 167)
  - Video 1123: A Piece of Cake (about Wayne Thiebaud) by Louise Lo (28'45") You Can't Lick Stamps in China by Nan June Park (28'39"), cuid2388; 545322 (Box 167)
  - Video 1124: Sichuan Acrobatic Feats Part I, cuid2389; 545321 (Box 167)
  - Video 1125: Sichuan Acrobatic Feats Part II, cuid2390; 545320 (Box 167)
  - Video 1126: Something is Rotten in Little Tokyo by Tom Kochiyama (37 min), cuid2391; 545319 (Box 167)
  - Video 1127: Strangle for Life, cuid2392; 545318 (Box 167)
  - Video 1128: Third World Cultural Perspective by La Mama Production Tape 1 of 2, cuid2393; 545317 (Box 167)
  - Video 1129: Third World Cultural Perspective by La Mama Production Tape 2 of 2, cuid2394; 545316 (Box 167)
  - Video 1130: With Silk Wings by Asian American Women at Work (30 min), cuid2395; 545315 (Box 167)
  - Video 1131: Bean Sprouts: Try it, You'll like it by Loni Ding, cuid2396; 545314 (Box 168)
  - Video 1132: The Boy Who Played with the Lion/Dragon by Sam Hom (Video Dub of Film), cuid2397; 545313 (Box 168)
  - Video 1133: East Meets West Channel 2 "The People", cuid2398; 545312 (Box 168)
  - Video 1134: Freckled Rice Excerpts by Stephen C. Ning, cuid2399; 545311 (Box 168)
  - Video 1135: Gold Dagger Romance Part I by RTV, 1984; cuid2400; 545310 (Box 168)
  - Video 1136: Heritage: Sail to the Southern Sea by RTHK, cuid2401; 545309 (Box 168)
  - Video 1137: Rebop: Ching Family, cuid2402; 545308 (Box 168)
  - Video 1138: Return of the Gangster, cuid2403; 545307 (Box 168)
  - Video 1139: Yellow Ball Workshop Children's Films, cuid2404; 545306 (Box 168)
  - Video 1140: "Golden Gate" Trailer, cuid2405; 545305 (Box 169)
  - Video 1141: Lick, 1995; cuid2406; 545304 (Box 169)
  - Video 1142: Requiem, cuid2407; 545303 (Box 169)
  - Video 1143: Say You Say Me, cuid2408; 545302 (Box 169)
  - Video 1144: The Shaolin Invincible Part I, cuid2409; 545301 (Box 169)
  - Video 1145: The Shaolin Invincible Part II, cuid2410; 545300 (Box 169)
  - Video 1146: "Stretchmark" Directed by Veena Cabreros-Sud, 1996; cuid2411; 545299 (Box 169)
  - Video 1147: War's Over, cuid2412; 545298 (Box 169)
  - Video 1148: "The Wedding Banquet" Trailer, cuid2413; 545297 (Box 169)
  - Videos 1149-1163: PALM (Philippine Alternative Media) tapes, 1981-1984; cuid2414; 545296 (Box 170)
  - Videos 1164- 1174 (small " tapes): WNYC Changing Faces of Chinatown tapes, cuid2415; 545295 (Box 171)
  - Video 1175: Asian Images in the Media by Bernice Chu, 1984; cuid2416; 545294 (Box 172)
  - Video 1176: CCTV Sample tape, cuid2417; 545293 (Box 172)
  - Video 1177: CCTV Sample tape, cuid2418; 545292 (Box 172)
  - Video 1178: Children's Film Series 1987, 1989; cuid2419; 545291 (Box 172)
  - Video 1179: Chinatown: 1984 (sample tape), cuid2420; 545290 (Box 172)
  - Video 1180: How to Become a Fascinating Speaker by Fu-Ding Cheng, 1989; cuid2421; 545289 (Box 172)
  - Video 1181: Tracking On (Master) (AAIVF comm..), cuid2422; 545288 (Box 172)
  - Video 1182: Tracking on (Raw Footage), cuid2423; 545287 (Box 172)
  - Video 1183: Vincent Chin "Remembrance Day" 6/19/83, 1984; cuid2424; 545286 (Box 172)
  - Video 1184: The Departure by Emiko Omori, 1984; cuid2425; 545285 (Box 173)
  - Video 1185: John by Art Nomura, 1989; cuid2426; 545284 (Box 173)
  - Video 1186: NAATA Press Conference: Portest WNET/13 censorship of Silkscreen series by Nancy Tong, 1984; cuid2427; 545283 (Box 173)
  - Video 1187: Stan Egi, comedian from David Letterman show; 1/31/85, cuid2428; 545282 (Box 173)
  - Video 1188: Two Comedians: Phil Nee and Stan Egi at the Middle of the Road (1/6/86), cuid2429; 545281 (Box 173)
  - Video 1189: Two Comedians: Phil Nee and Stan Egi at the Middle of the Road (1/6/86), cuid2430; 545280 (Box 173)
  - Video 1190: Two Comedians: Phil Nee and Stan Egi at the Middle of the Road (1/6/86), cuid2431; 545279 (Box 173)
  - Video 1191: Wallow (Silent) by Eiko and Koma, 1989; cuid2432; 545278 (Box 173)
  - Video 1192: We Have to Link, 1982; cuid2433; 545277 (Box 173)
  - Video 1193: "Ablutions" by S. Ashraf Mfer, 1993; cuid2434; 545276 (Box 174)
  - Video 1194: All Orientals Look the Same by Valerie Soe, cuid2435; 545275 (Box 174)
  - Video 1195: The Departure by Emiko Omori, cuid2436; 545274 (Box 174)
  - Video 1196: Husk by Eiko and koma, cuid2437; 545273 (Box 174)
  - Video 1197: Keyboard Dance by Ye Sook Rhee, cuid2438; 545272 (Box 174)
  - Video 1198: The Only Language She Knows by Steven Okazaki, cuid2439; 545271 (Box 174)
  - Video 1199: Snipers in the Trees by Curtis Choy 1985, cuid2440; 545270 (Box 174)
  - Video 1200: Stereotypes of Asian in the Media by ACV (AAE), cuid2441; 545269 (Box 174)
  - Video 1201: The Year of the Ox: The 1975 Chinatown Livestock Show by Curtis Choy, cuid2442; 545268 (Box 174)
  - Video 1202: After Image of Vanished Ways Featuring Sandy Granich, by Daryl Sujakawg, cuid2443; 545267 (Box 175)
  - Video 1203: Aquino Memorial Mass, September 1983, Shot by L. Remoador, M. Gener, R. Hodel, D. Miyazake, Produced by PALM (Philippine Alternative Media) a division of ACV, cuid2444; 545266 (Box 175)
  - Video 1204: Building Blocks and Tsumiki by Saiki Hiromu, cuid2445; 545265 (Box 175)
  - Video 1205: Ch'unhyang: Part 1, Tape 1, cuid2446; 545264 (Box 175)
  - Video 1206: Chinatown: 1984 (excerpt from part 1 of a 4 part series), cuid2447; 545263 (Box 175)
  - Video 1207: Coverage on the Year of the Dragon, 8/16/85, on CBS, NBC, ABC, Entertainment Tonight, cuid2448; 545262 (Box 175, Box TAM Shared Access Box 1)
  - Video 1208: "Marco Polo" Clips from NBC Production Featuring Ying Ruocheng as Kublai Khan, cuid2449; 545261 (Box 175)
  - Video 1209: Q it Up by Spencer Naka sako 1985, cuid2450; 545260 (Box 175)
  - Video 1210: The Electronic Sounds of Russell Baba (excerpts), cuid2451; 545259 (Box 175)
  - Video 1211: 1984 AAIVF footage, cuid2452; 545258 (Box 176)
  - Video 1212: CCTV (Chinese), cuid2453; 545257 (Box 176)
  - Video 1213: Charlie Chin, cuid2454; 545256 (Box 176)
  - Video 1214: Charlie Chin, cuid2455; 545255 (Box 176)
  - Video 1215: Chase scene tape #1, cuid2456; 545254 (Box 176)
  - Video 1216: HK Fashion Show CCTV, cuid2457; 545253 (Box 176)
  - Video 1217: An hon Kong Voyage by Sam Hom, 1979; cuid2458; 545252 (Box 176)
  - Video 1218: Josephine Cheng, cuid2459; 545251 (Box 176)
  - Video 1219: With Liberty and Justice for All, cuid2460; 545250 (Box 176)
  - Videos 1220-1228 (small " tapes): ACV Video Training Workshop tapes, cuid2461; 545249 (Box 177)
  - Video 1229: 1987 Video Production Workshop, cuid2462; 545248 (Box 178)
  - Video 1230: 1987 Video Production Workshop, cuid2463; 545247 (Box 178)
  - Video 1231: 1987 Video Production Workshop, cuid2464; 545246 (Box 178)
  - Video 1232: 1988 Video Production Workshop, cuid2465; 545245 (Box 178)
  - Video 1233: 1989 Workshop, cuid2466; 545244 (Box 178)
  - Video 1234: 1989 Video Production Workshop, cuid2467; 545243 (Box 178)
  - Video 1235: Asian Cinevision Presents Chinese American Television (sample tape), cuid2468; 545242 (Box 178)
  - Video 1236: Black for editing use only, cuid2469; 545241 (Box 178)
  - Video 1237: Standby tape, cuid2470; 545240 (Box 178)
  - Video 1238: Asian Films: Asian Film Series, 1986; cuid2471; 545239 (Box 179)
  - Video 1239: "Asian Cinevision Presents" Trailer, 1988; cuid2472; 545238 (Box 179)
  - Video 1240: Asian Cinevision, 1990; cuid2473; 545237 (Box 179)
  - Video 1241: Woo Art, cuid2474; 545236 (Box 179)
  - Video 1242: opening trailer, cuid2475; 545235 (Box 179)
  - Video 1243: Asian Cinevision, cuid2476; 545234 (Box 179)
  - Video 1244: "Videoscape", cuid2477; 545233 (Box 179)
  - Video 1245: "Kim Chi's Vietnam", cuid2478; 545232 (Box 179)
  - Video 1246: What Do You Know About Korea? (1996), cuid2479; 545231 (Box 179)
  - Video 1247: 60 flowers, 70 capsules, 80 digits by Arturo Cubacub, cuid2480; 545230 (Box 180)
  - Video 1248: Alpha Echo, The Journey all by Ruby Truly, cuid2481; 545229 (Box 180)
  - Video 1249: ES (12:00), Pinoys in Berlin (4:00 min) Both by Raymond Red, cuid2482; 545228 (Box 180)
  - Video 1250: Good McMorning America by Florence Yoo, cuid2483; 545227 (Box 180)
  - Video 1251: Hit Your Own Back by Taka Izmura, cuid2484; 545226 (Box 180)
  - Video 1252: Kinesthesia by Indu Krishnan (3:25 min), Can Dance by Ye Sook Rhee (4:00), Lament by Eiko and Koma (8:10), My Prison by HiroyaSakurai (3:30), cuid2485; 545225 (Box 180)
  - Video 1253: On Edge, Read Only (Phosphor) Memory, After Image: TTLS, In Plus/Pulse all by Norie Sato, cuid2486; 545224 (Box 180)
  - Video 1254: Tigerfly Inc./ Arnie Wong '87, cuid2487; 545223 (Box 180)
  - Video 1255: Francesca Soans, cuid2488; 545222 (Box 180)
  - Video 1256: Unidentified, cuid2489; 545221 (Box 181)
  - Video 1257: Death of an Immigrant, cuid2490; 545220 (Box 181)
  - Video 1258: Edward Akira Radtke films, cuid2491; 545219 (Box 181)
  - Video 1260: No Starch Please (2 scenes) by Ann Yen, cuid2492; 545218 (Box 181)
  - Video 1261: Rory O'Shea selected scenes, cuid2493; 545217 (Box 181)
  - Video 1262: Zu: Warrior from the Magic Mountain, cuid2494; 545216 (Box 181)
  - Video 1263: UC6, Unidentified (small " tape), cuid2495; 545215 (Box 181)
  - Video 1264: Unidentified, Chinese (small " tape), cuid2496; 545214 (Box 181)
  - Video 1265: Unidentified (small " tape, cuid2497; 545213 (Box 181)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2498; 545212 (Box 182)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2499; 545211 (Box 183)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2500; 545210 (Box 184)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2501; 545209 (Box 185)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2502; 545208 (Box 186)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2503; 545207 (Box 187)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2504; 545206 (Box 188)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2505; 545205 (Box 189)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2506; 545204 (Box 190)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2507; 545203 (Box 191)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2508; 545202 (Box 192)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2509; 545201 (Box 193)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2510; 545200 (Box 194)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2511; 545199 (Box 195)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2512; 545198 (Box 196)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2513; 545197 (Box 197)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2514; 545196 (Box 198)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2515; 545195 (Box 199)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2516; 545194 (Box 200)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2517; 545193 (Box 201)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2518; 545192 (Box 202)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2519; 545191 (Box 203)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2520; 545190 (Box 204)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2521; 545189 (Box 205)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2522; 545188 (Box 206)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2523; 545187 (Box 207)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2524; 545186 (Box 208)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2525; 545185 (Box 209)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2526; 545184 (Box 210)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2527; 545183 (Box 211)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2528; 545182 (Box 212)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2529; 545181 (Box 213)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2530; 545180 (Box 214)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2531; 545179 (Box 215)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2532; 545178 (Box 216)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2533; 545177 (Box 217)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2534; 545176 (Box 218)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (VHS), cuid2535; 545175 (Box 219)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (Beta), cuid2536; 545174 (Box 220)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (Beta, U-Matic), cuid2537; 545173 (Box 221)
  - Video submissions for Asian American International Film Festival (Beta, U-Matic), cuid2538; 545172 (Box 222)
  - 2004-2007 films: Eve and the Fire Horse (2005), Who's Camus Anyway? (2006), Rain Dogs, Seven Women - Jade #2 (3 copies), Incense (3 copies), Taking Father Home (2005), cuid2539; 545171 (Box 223)
  - Harsh Canvas: The life of Henry Sugimoto, One on One with Maggie Cheung, cuid2540; 545170 (Box 224)
  - 25th AAIFF films: 6 Betacam (large), 15 Betacam (small), 5 VHS, cuid2541; 545169 (Box 225)
  - 12 large Betacam SP videos, cuid2542; 545168 (Box 226)
  - 5 U-Matics, 11VHS, cuid2543; 545167 (Box 228)
  - 35 VHS, 9 miniDVs, cuid2544; 545166 (Box 229)
  - Bridge Mechanical Final Issue - Never went to press, cuid2545; 545165 (Box 230)
  - photo: Film Festival 1994-1997, other film festivals and ACV events, cuid2546; 545164 (Box 231)
  - photo: film stills, cuid2547; 545163 (Box 232)
  - photo: slides (news slides), film stills, cuid2548; 545162 (Box 233)
  - photo: Children film series photos, cuid2549; 545161 (Box 234)
  - AAIFF, bridge mag photos, film stills, cuid2550; 545160 (Box 235)
  - Film festival photos 1 '90-92, stills 198, cuid2551; 545159 (Box 236)
  - photo: AAIFF photos, cuid2552; 545158 (Box 237)
  - photo: all stills 9/6/06, cuid2553; 545157 (Box 238)
  - 16th AAIFF trailer 35mm, cuid2554; 545156 (Box 239)
  - AAIFF Trailers 1998-2000 35 mm, cuid2555; 545155 (Box 239)
  - Maya 35mm, cuid2556; 545154 (Box 239)
  - Death and Peanuts 16mm, cuid2557; 545153 (Box 239)
  - Shorts from Mowelfund: Melvin and Mekka, Child of Manila, LAHO; A Veteran's Story; The Eagle Patrol; Matricide; to Bengali Express Final Print; Overture: Linh from Vietnam, cuid2558; 545152 (Box 242)
  - Good Kisser; Nene; Isaak, cuid2559; 545151 (Box 243)
  - 16th AAIFF Trailer; Now and Then Here and There by Fei Sing Loo; The Conductor by Jessica Yu; My America reel 2of 3; The Colours of the Sun Apricoss Swedish Film Institute; ACV Trailer 2000; Woo Art Intl ACUOpen AAIFF 94, cuid2560; 545150 (Box 244)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 4 of 8, cuid2561; 545149 (Box 245)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 3 of 8, cuid2562; 545148 (Box 246)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 2 of 8, cuid2563; 545147 (Box 247)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 1 of 8, cuid2564; 545146 (Box 248)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 5 of 8, cuid2565; 545145 (Box 249)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 6 of 8, cuid2566; 545144 (Box 250)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 7 of 8, cuid2567; 545143 (Box 251)
  - Arisa by Kalyana Shira 8 of 8, cuid2568; 545142 (Box 252)
  - Raha by Jervekopi, cuid2569; 545141 (Box 253)
  - "16" 1 of 5, cuid2570; 545140 (Box 254)
  - "16" 2 of 5, cuid2571; 545139 (Box 255)
  - "16" 3 of 5, cuid2572; 545138 (Box 256)
  - "16" 4 of 5, cuid2573; 545137 (Box 257)
  - "16" 5 of 5, cuid2574; 545136 (Box 258)